Hey, I'm totally stuffed now!
What was that, anyway?
Jiggle...
That practically bucket-sized
dish we just had?
It's bucket pudding!
Woo-hoo! Woo-hoo!
You've still got room
for more, right, Sophie?
I do, naturally.
What do you mean, naturally?
What's this?
Oh, the cargo is stuck in here.
Excuse me...
Whose wagon is this?
If you can't pass through,
you should take the main road.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry!
You're a centaur!
Indeed I am.
My name is...
Huh? Is that you, Dione?
Oh! Great—
The fact that I was the
Great Hero is a secret!
Got it?!
Do you two know each other?
Huh?
Well, maybe we do, or maybe we don't...
Which is it?
Great— I mean, Blade and I go way back!
Back when Blade was the Great— wait, no!
More importantly!
What are you gonna do about this cargo?
Oh, that's right.
If you'd like, we'd be happy to help out.
Yes.
Leave it to me!
We dragons are powerful!
I would appreciate your help.
Are you all members of Blade's party?
No! They're my friends.
I see.
So? Where are we hauling this?
Oh, yes. That'd be...
Oh! Took you long enough!
It was the old fart's cargo?
That's lèse-majesté, Blade.
Your Majesty.
I've brought it here, as per your command.
Good going!
On that note, I have your
next assignment ready.
Yes!
As you wish!
Okay!
Starting today, you will be teaching at
Rosewood Academy as an instructor.
What?!
That came out of nowhere!
Blade is well aware of her abilities.
She should be more than qualified
to act as your instructor.
Well, yeah...
Well, then, best of luck to you!
Yes!
I look forward to teaching you!
Great— wait, no!
Blade!
Is this really gonna work?
Hm...
I look in your eyes, and I'm met with
A brand-new me and dream
Bravery? Naturally?
Polar opposites within the heart
But, you know, wanting to have both
That's the saga of human nature
Oh no, don't mind me
Go ahead, and so on, you know the rest
A little more? Wait, even harder?!
Going overboard much?
Those selfish emotions deep down
Bringing them to light is
what friendship's about
Spending adolescence duking it out with pals
I don't wanna lose
We're off to the cutting edge moment
Fight with best friends, and leave no regrets
You should laugh, since
you look best with a smile
On the ropes?! No matter
what we face, et cetera
Just sit back and enjoy it
Whatever may come, I'll
be here to protect you
Episode 6
The General and the Sacred Bird
What's going on here?
Wait, who's that?
Is that God Iron?
Sure is.
Back in the day, we used boulders instead.
I thought God Iron was indestructible.
Oh, is that what's normal?
It's not just destroyed, it's melting...
Wow...
I'm finally feeling all warmed up!
Okay, let's begin class!
Introduce yourself first!
You're right!
I am Dione!
Dione, the Demon Lance!
If any of you feel confident enough,
take up your sword and face me!
Wait, you're not here to fight a duel!
Dione, the Demon Lance?
What?!
Are you General Dione,
commander of the top cavalry corps?!
General?!
A bonafide hero!
Someone so accomplished is
going to be our teacher?
Oh, no!
Before the Great Hero, I'm not...
Ah!
Hey!
So, Miss Dione, you've had the privilege
of seeing the Great Hero fight in person!
W-W-Well, that's all in the past...
But then how does someone
like you know Blade?
Do you think Miss Dione is
acquaintances with Blade?
Hm...
Consider me interested.
Parent, that tickles!
Stop squirming already!
No weird noises!
I always just bathe in cold water,
but this is pretty good, too!
How's everything feel, Sis?
Let's get that sweat wiped off.
I'm in heaven!
Have you known Blade for a long time, Sis?
I-I-I only met Blade the other day!
Back then, you said you two went way back.
Th-That's, well...
Hey, Sis.
I'd love to hear you talk about
what Blade was like in the past.
I'd be interested in that, too!
Please tell us, Sis!
That's the spot!
Keep going, right there!
It feels good!
If you want it here...
Hey!
I-If it isn't the Great— I mean, Blade!
We were so close, too.
Hey, Blade!
Why are you in here like it's nothing?!
Well, who else is going to wash Cu's hair?
Calm down, Anna.
Blade is mentally similar to
a five-year-old, you know.
There!
Huh?
See?
Don't give me that!
What are you doing, Yessica?!
Five years old, you say...
That's about how old Blade
was when I first met him.
Hey, Dione!
Oh?
When he was as old as I am now?
I'd love to hear all about it.
When I first met Blade...
he was so ferocious,
I thought he was a wild animal.
Huh...
He could barely speak, and it
seems he thought I was a horse,
so he sunk his teeth into my bottom.
Aghhhh
I was still inexperienced back then,
and I really was one step
away from becoming dinner.
Man, that's just like Blade.
A few years after that,
after training my mind and body,
I became worthy of joining forces
with the Great Hero himself!
So the rumors that you fought with
the Great Hero are true, General?
You betcha!
Relax.
No one can tell she's talking about you.
Huh?
I've even let the Great Hero ride on my back!
Whoa!
However, he did not let me join him
for the fight against the Demon King.
I wasn't able to act as
his steed to the very end.
In self-reproach, I took it
as a sign of my own weakness,
and now I strive to train myself further.
I think that's remarkable.
Are you sure no one noticed?
Yes.
Everyone thinks the Great Hero is much older.
Ah! Makes sense.
So it's our little secret.
Well, you see...
I was found out.
Several days later!
What should we bring back as a gift for Sis?
Cabbage, maybe?
She eats them whole, you know.
Hey, Blade.
So, really, what is your
relationship with her?
Well, you see...
What?!
A simurgh?!
What's a simurgh, again?
It's one of the four
Continental Sacred Birds!
Oh, so it's like a thunderbird, or a phoenix.
But what's a simurgh doing
here in the royal capital?
Well, I'm sure it won't attack us,
as long as we don't provoke it.
That's true.
There are no records of
them attacking humans.
Earnest!
Huh?
Oh, no! We need to stop it!
Keep your fighting spirit in check!
Okay! Okay!
Two of them...
Are you okay?!
Are those two simurghs mates?
And why?
I thought they didn't attack people.
It almost looked like...
they were after that wagon, not people.
The wagon?
Could it be that...
I bet that jerk's got
something to do with this.
That jerk
That
jerk
A warm bath is really something else!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
We need to talk!
What's the matter?
You seem upset.
Exactly what have you been hiding from us?!
So that doesn't count as lèse-majesté?
The town was under attack!
Please explain what's going on here!
What makes you so sure it has to do with me?
The simurgh attacked a freight wagon.
I see.
Dione also happened to be
pulling a freight wagon.
That's true.
Your Majesty!
Just what was in that freight wagon?!
Oh, that?
It was...
Egg
An egg.
You stole a simurgh egg?!
Don't make such accusatory statements.
I was just borrowing it for a bit.
Yeah, and the parents are
absolutely furious as a result!
Gil.
Don't you think you should
thoroughly explain the situation?
Yeah, guess so.
The situation?
Yes.
There are two conditions required
for a simurgh egg to hatch.
The first is keeping at the same height
as the 10,000-year-old sacred tree.
The second is to bathe in the light of the
setting sun at the moment of hatching.
However, it seems those parents
are new to making nests.
They picked a poor location for a nest,
and the egg wouldn't have hatched if left alone.
So you were trying to help them?
That's the pretext, anyway.
Actually, I was thinking it would be
good practical training for all of you.
A-Are you an idiot?
Are you an idiot?!
Good, tell it like it is!
That said!
It's true that, at this rate,
the egg will not hatch.
If you want to be a hero...
no, what lies beyond...
Go and save that simurgh!
When is it supposed to hatch?!
Tomorrow!
What?!
The next day!
Attention!
Listen up for this briefing
from your commander!
Today, we face simurghs in combat!
Our goal in this fight is not to win!
It is to buy us time until sunset,
and to hide this egg from its parents!
The parents are in a state of frenzy.
If they spot the egg, they might
destroy it in their fervor!
We'll keep the egg concealed
until the very last minute,
then lift it up via elevator
to the top of the tower!
By doing so, the egg will successfully hatch!
We'll make sure it hatches!
Have no fear!
Have faith in what we've
accomplished up to this point!
Have faith in yourself!
U-Um...
What do we do if...
...we can't have faith in ourselves?
It's okay if you can't
have faith in yourselves.
I have faith in you.
Y-Yes!
Everyone! Here we go!
Are the citizens safe?
We've evacuated everyone in this district!
That's a relief.
Look at you go, handsome!
Leonard!
Yessica!
Clay!
Take that!
Shoot!
Figures that wouldn't work!
Okay, now's our chance!
These wires are made of God Iron.
Normally, it'd be impossible to sever them!
Normally...
Eh?
Ehh?!
Ehhh?!
It's pulling up entire buildings?!
That's absurd!
But that bought us some time.
Keep it up!
Claire, take care of him!
Yes!
Have a taste of this!
How's that?
Give up?!
It's pretty fearsome...
Maria! Undo your braids!
Y-Y-Yes!
You would use the Demon King?
Very well! Use me how you see fit!
Satan Levin!
So it won't pierce through a sacred bird?
You're not getting away!
Flame of Asmodeus!
All outta gas...
Bucket pudding!
Jiggle...
Back in action!
We did it!
Is everyone okay?
Yes, we're fine.
All that's left is...
What?!
Don't tell me... it stopped?
It sure did stop.
Yep, it stopped.
Oh, no! It noticed the egg!
Blade, you get the egg.
Wait, but...
That's right, Blade!
We'll handle things here!
You go on!
Great Hero Blade!
We'll handle them!
You go on ahead!
Blade!
Remember what you said.
Have faith in us!
You're right.
This is terrifying!
It's harder than I thought to
only use 15% of my strength!
Great Hero!
Come, get on my back!
What? I thought you weren't
going to help out!
Nope!
His Majesty gave strict
orders not to lend a hand.
However...
I'm just letting you ride on my back.
No hands involved!
I was told just now to let them
handle it, and go on ahead.
It reminded me of back then,
in a lot of ways.
You're not alone anymore,
are you, Great Hero?
No, I'm not.
It was just me when I fought the Demon King.
But now, I have lots of friends!
And of course, you're one of them, Dione!
Yes!
We need to carry this?
No way!
Ain't happening!
Hm, let me think...
Great Hero!
Hold onto it nice and tight, just like that!
Dione, what are you doing?!
I'm just giving you a push!
Here we go, Great Hero!
H-Hey! Dione!
We made it!
Good work.
Welcome to the finish line!
I knew you'd be able to do it!
After all, you are the Great Hero!
I'm not a hero anymore!
I only made it thanks to everyone's help.
Hey, wait!
It's the other simurgh!
Yep.
Looks like it's my time to shine now.
What?
I, Gilgamesh Soulmaker,
declare here in my name!
A life owed shall be repaid by new life!
I'll be paying you back, right here!
A simurgh once saved Gil's life.
Huh?
Come, simurgh.
It's been playing on his
mind this whole time.
Accept my gratitude and take
this new life into your talons!
But thanks to you,
he can finally repay his debt.
Thank you, Blade.
Seriously?!
Ow!
You should have just told us from the start!
That hurts!
Sheesh, you just can't be honest!
Stop that! Ow!
Wait, does it look angrier now?
It seems that way.
Watch out!
Artificial Great Hero Power.
Five seconds remaining.
That's more than enough!
Dragon Eater!
I can't move a finger...
So heavy...
I'm lighter than Earnest, at least.
Blade! The egg!
Oh dear!
It was twins!
No wonder it was so heavy.
Huh?
Why are they staring at me?
They're imprinting.
They see Blade as their parent.
Ah! You've got more children now!
What are you gonna do about this?!
Call me your big sister!
Wait, why are you getting
touchy with Sophie?!
Now then, what to do...
Several days later!
H-Hey now!
Please, do as I say!
Okay? Okay?!
Let it fly however it wants!
I-I know that!
I know...
Parent!
Man, looks like I've made even more friends!
The sunny disposition that
brings a smile to your face
As well as the heroic sense of justice
They may be a part of me,
but that's not all there is
That image of me
Has taken on a life of its own
Hey, wait up
Won't you be friends with me?
Let's shake hands, another self of mine
The wounds we cannot bear alone
The dangers that we keep hidden
We're all hiding them within
Standing ready to strike
The shadow lurking beneath the light
The muffled sounds coming from my lips
They make me feel that I am alive
It's a sign
Next Time
The Springtime of Life at Rosewood Academy